They're just four little level 45 kids. Wipe them out and be done with it.
Have you ever seen "kids" like this reach level 45?
Don't be fooled by their random appearances.
Let's finish this quickly. Territory war is about to start.
Uncle, please let us go.
Who are you calling "Uncle"!!
Can't let them go!
Level 45 clearly means they've accepted a threshold mission.
One of us is their target.
Meow.
[Just focust on running away.]
Hm?
Even though they're low level, we still have to take them out.
Understood.
Why can I understand that?
What now? Who goes there?
Awen, you go.
Understood.
Stop them!
After them!
Catch them!
Just keep running forward!
Protect me! I need five uninterrupted seconds!
There's one more teleport charge!
Go!
Xiaohei! Get back here!
We're running out of time...
Interrupt it!
Go!
Only two kilometers away.
This way!
Can't we log out?!
No, we've engaged in combat.
We need two minutes
out of combat to log out.
Found them! Over here!
Try to dodge! Don't engage!
Coordinates.
It's "Tracking"! That means we can't break combat.
The skill lasts at least ten minutes.
Logging out isn't realistic anymore! We need to fight back!
How?
This way! The terrain is complex.
Why didn't that guy just take us out directly?
Damn, he's underestimating us!
Xiaohei, do you see them?
One of those four is our target, I'll leave it to you.
Okay.
Blast them! Don't let them break combat!
Fall back! Everyone below level 60, fall back!
He's hunting!
What's going on!
Healer! Stall him!
Healer my ass! He oneshots everyone!
Mission complete!
Leveled up again.
At this rate, leveling through roaming combat should be fine.
What?!
Gen!
Level 145?
Why is there a player this high level?
Xiaohei.
Let's hope there aren't any more...
What?
Why can't I kill them?!
So scary...
Over a hundred?!
Are all of these over level 100!?
Gen!!
Shanxin!
Xiaohei!
Xiaohei.
Don't die.
Stop chasing!
How's it going?
Tracking landed. He can't break combat for twenty minutes.
Good, share it with the whole team and open the Barrier Gate.
Is that necessary? The territory war is about to start!
If we go to the territory war now,
we already know what'll happen.
Where's the fun in that?
This is clearly more interesting.
You couldn't beat him?
If it weren't for my artifact, I'd have died hundreds of times already.
So you're saying we're not safe either?
Are we playing this game to be safe?
But, come to think of it...
If he really could take out all seven of us...
then he'd be the highest-level player on the server.
“Logout unavailable”
Your tracking skill's accuracy is way too low!
It's a hundred-meter range. What more do you want?
We can't find him like this.
Confirmed, he's in the tree.
He can't leave this area now. He must be really anxious.
He's extremely fast. The barrier lasts thirty minutes.
Once the barrier's gone, we might not be able to catch him.
He's as fast as us, but he's way too agile.
In this terrain, we can't catch him.
On open ground, he wouldn't be able to escape.
I'll be the main tank.
Liusuan, Luanbu, Xiaorui.
You three handle containment.
Geshao, Axian, Tuobi.
You three use area of effect slows.
To be safe, stack it three times.
Don't worry about wasting them.
Got it.
Why can't we log out yet?
He was hit by the tracking skill. You can see it on his status.
Eighteen minutes left. Plus, they used a barrier item.
He can't leave this area for half an hour.
Xiaohei probably doesn't check the skill panel, right?
If he can avoid further contact,
then in eighteen minutes he'll be able to log out.
Can we tell him?
No, there's no way to contact someone from outside the game.
It's all up to him. There's nothing we can do to help.
But there is one advantage now.
Oh?
Without us splitting the XP,
he'll level up really fast.
Why did you take out his teammates first?
We didn't know it'd turn out like this.
Obviously we'd take out anyone we could.
None of us can die.
If we do, he'll become incredibly powerful.
Everyone ready?
One minute left.
Seven level 100s ganging up on one level-50.
And this is us being cautious.
What exclusive item do you think he has? I'm really curious.
I think it's reaction speed. He might have an item that enhances that.
None of us are short on items.
His mechanics are what really matter.
After we catch him...
let's add him as a friend.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Can't get out. Can't log out either...
They're afraid of me leveling up...
Low levels aren't a threat.
Since I can't escape...
I'll fight back.
Hey hey hey! Go easy on those! That's a rare item!
Relax, it's those are just a distraction.
Almost there.
Got it.
What did Xiaohei get hit with?
No idea. I can't see anything unusual.
Over there! Go go go!
Why isn't he leveling up?
Get ready! Here we go!
What's this?
Didn't that guy die?
It's a passive skill. After being killed, the killer gets a debuff.
Right now it shows "Heavy."
But why isn't Xiaohei leveling up yet?
Hurry! Only five minutes left!
How did this happen?
I didn't expect that guy could revive. There's actually a skill like that!
Why isn't Xiaohei leveling up?
What does "five minutes" refer to?
Where did he go?
This way!
What's going on?
Watch out!
Don't 1v1 him! Watch the heals!
Don't let him get the upperhand! Stall him!
Heal! After him!
Damn!
Don't come any closer.
He's gone.
Where to?
This is bad.
He's close by. His ability has a short range.
Everyone be careful.
The skill he got hit with earlier probably suppresses leveling.
There's a skill like that?
Yeah.
He should still have gotten the XP, but he can't level while the debuff is active.
They must've been counting down the timelimit.
If Xiaohei can hold out,
he'll level up like crazy.
Watch out! A projectile!
Use this item first!
So annoying!
He's moving.
Stop chasing!
Heal, stall him!
You're really strong.
Add me as a friend.
One minute left.
Yeah, let's kill him.
It'd be bad if he actually
turned the tables on us.
Hope we run into you again sometime.
Huh?
Mas...
Master...
Xiaohei.
You failed.
Sorry, but I'm taking this one with me.
Level 13?
What kind of people are these!
Hmph.
Take him out first!
Go!
What the hell...
Damn!
Hm?
I'm taking him. Here's an item as compensation.
I'm sure you'll like it.
So little damage...
I didn't lose any HP.
Was that iron ball an artifact too?
Quick, see what he gave us!
So greedy.
You're not going to look?
Look, look, look.
Why is it black?
We must have been shut out.
That was Xiaohei's master just now...
And they won't let us watch.
I really want to know what they're saying.
Me too!
Hey...
Was the game fun?
While you were doing this quest, were you happy?
If...
If this were a real mission, they'd really all be dead.
I feel like I can't do anything. I have to rely on them for everything.
All I can do is fight...
But I couldn't even protect them...
But you're good at fighting.
Just like me.
You were happy not because of the mission, but because you were with your friends, right?
You wanted to become an Executor just so you could follow your master.
I designed this mission. I thought you might not complete it,
but I didn't expect you to fail so quickly.
You didn't even get to experience how hard the follow-up dungeon missions are.
But this is what an Executor's daily life is like.
Then...
Do you feel happy when you do missions, Master?
No, I don't.
Then why do you do them?
Because it's my responsibility.
Then it can be my responsibility too.
The Guild is very strong right now.
It's not yet time for little ones like you to bear that responsibility.
Tell me, what do you want to do most right now?
When I ask you that,
what's the first thought that comes to your mind?
I...
I want to learn to read with Xiaobai.
That's great.
Let's do that, then.
I don't want to...
Why are you crying?
I'll be there too.
Really?
Yeah, just like before.
You know? In human households,
the kids go to school and the adults go to work.
Then after school, I'll come home too.
What's "after school"?
You'll... find out once you've learned to read.
Oh...
Meeting and parting, joy and sadness
If one day you truly want to become an Executor, come take the test again.
Is that okay?
Excitement and confusedness, hope and despair
Of course.
Why won't he wake up?
Doesn't matter what tomorrow will be like
You've made a lot of good friends.
Yeah!
Be with me, singing together softly
Treasure them well.
I will.
On a quiet night, we're singing a quiet song
You softly tell me about your dreams
On this starless, moonless night
I'm here by your side
Seems like he finally mastered the new space.
Yeah, seems like he's adapted.
There's too much of sweet, bitter and sour
You forgot about joy and sadness
My happiness is in your hands
Be with me, don't wander anymore
On a quiet night, we're singing a quiet song
You softly tell me about your dreams
Tonight, when the whole world is sleeping
I'm here by your side
Doesn't matter what tomorrow will be like
Be with me, singing together softly
What?
Dongdong...
is missing?
Stay with me aruite yukou ishikoro wo kette
Stay with me - let's walk on, kicking pebbles as we go
Yukisaki wa kitto kimagure demo
Our destination may be whimsical
Hana no kaori wo ryoute ni
But with the scent of flowers in both hands
kore kara deau kimi e to
I’ll carry it to the you I’ve yet to meet
Wait for me hanashi wo shiyou kata wo narabete
Wait for me — let’s talk, side by side
Hajimemashite wa gikochinaku temo
Even if our first “hello” is a little awkward
Mochiyotta hako aketara
When we open the boxes we’ve brought
Tsumekon da yume wo wakeaou
Let’s share the dreams we’ve packed inside
Mata ashita tte atarimae ni kawaseru hibi ga
The days when we can casually say “See you tomorrow”
Itoshikute hakanasugite
Are so precious and so fleeting
Omoi wa kitto kienai
Those feelings will never fade away
Sora wo nagareru kumo ni wa oitsukenai kedo
We can’t catch up to the clouds drifting across the sky
Ame ni natte hana wo tsukete kitto boku wo yonderu
But they’ll turn to rain, bloom into flowers
Kitto boku wo yonderu
And surely, they’re calling out to me